[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 57, "question": "Do we know that for a fact?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 58, "answer": "I know it because I know the market pretty well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iowa", "New Hampshire", "South Carolina"]}, "docId": "120112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "EX", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 70, "question": "Why is that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 71, "answer": "I guess maybe they've gotten into it for a while in -- they sort of begin in Iowa, then they go to New Hampshire, it's a little bit restrained there, and they get to South Carolina.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 83, "question": "Armageddon really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 84, "answer": "That may be overstated a little.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 101, "question": "Are you moving towards Mitt Romney?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "NNS", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 102, "answer": "I'm not moving at any direction at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CC", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 115, "question": "Can this make a difference in the way that Mitt Romney's super PACs really hammered Newt Gingrich's popularity?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "NNP", "RB", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 116, "answer": "You can -- you can emphasize and sympathize with Newt.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney", "Newt Gingrich"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "Or was it all fair in love and electoral war?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "It was -- some of it was unfair.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 135, "question": "He wins all four, he's there, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 136, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "CC", "RB", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 137, "question": "You would assume so?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 138, "answer": "I would say, and then practically --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Santorum"]}, "docId": "120112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 144, "question": "Is it Gingrich simply on (INAUDIBLE) money?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "NNP", "RB", "IN", "CD", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 145, "answer": "Gingrich or Santorum.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 190, "question": "What are his weaknesses?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 191, "answer": "I think you go after him on the economy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "Where has he genuinely had success?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "He's had success with terrorism, a success and failures with terrorism, but he's had success in the ones that are quite obvious.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 222, "question": "What do you make of the furor surrounding it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 223, "answer": "Typical.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 238, "question": "Or is it just glorified tittle-tattle?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 239, "answer": "Somewhere in between.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "EX", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 265, "question": "Did you expect it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "Well, actually there's been a lot of praise and excitement for the book.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "120112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "''", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 287, "question": "As she says, how do you know what's going on in their head?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 288, "answer": "Well, I reported on her for about the same way I've been reporting on her for five years in the \"New York Times,\" which is the Obama inner circle really let me in for this book.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", ":", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 300, "question": "How would you know that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 301, "answer": "Well, because her -- I was -- her aides gave me access.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJS", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 330, "question": "You must be disappointed, as a \"New York Times\" journalist, that your book is being characterized as a critical attack in many ways on the First Lady, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "IN", "DT", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 331, "answer": "Well, you know, most people who have read the book think it's a pretty flattering portrait of her.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington"]}, "docId": "120112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "Why are they doing this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "That is something I think a lot of reporters in Washington don't necessarily understand.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NNS", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 373, "question": "Are you slightly sad that the book is being spun, for whatever reason, in this very negative way against the First Lady?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBN", ",", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 374, "answer": "I do think you're on to an excellent question, because the political culture is so nasty and negative that I think there is a good question about if you work really hard on an honest portrayal of these people, that shows their successes and failures and their strengths and their weaknesses, you are at risk of being attacked for that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michelle Obama"]}, "docId": "120112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "RB", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 378, "question": "Do we want to live in a world where -- where that doesn't exist?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", ":", "WRB", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 379, "answer": "ORGAN: No, I guess my only point journalistically is that you are relying on other people to tell you how Michelle Obama, in particular, has been feeling throughout this book.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 384, "question": "I mean you would accept that, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 385, "answer": "Well, let me tell you about one scene in the book that I find very poignant.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "If the First Lady's watching this, and I'm sure it's on her nightly viewing schedule, would you express any regret to her in the way this is all being portrayed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "VBG", "DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "Oh, well, you know, I can't take the responsibility for what people are saying on TV shows, when they haven't read the book and they haven't studied this.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["First Lady"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "When you saw this video as a soldier first, I guess, what was your reaction to it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "You know, first and foremost, you know, that is not anything that we were ever taught to do as soldiers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", ":", "RB", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 445, "question": "Are you surprised that sometimes in the heat of battle soldiers, even the finest Marines, go over the top like this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "DT", "JJS", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 446, "answer": "No, I mean, I don't think that -- again, this isn't appropriate behavior.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Marines"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "You think it's more callous than that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "No, I have no idea.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "CC", "NN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 480, "question": "And in that kind of video, they ruin everything, don't they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 481, "answer": "YNCH: Yeah, I mean, obviously you can look out and tell that, you know, that's not appropriate behavior in any manner.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 499, "question": "It's just incredibly disappointing, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 500, "answer": "It is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ":"], "qSentId": 505, "question": "Should they be kicked out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "Again --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", ":"], "qSentId": 507, "question": "The perpetrators?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "I think we should find out from the whole entire case of what the actual back story is --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 517, "question": "It must be an awful thing for them, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 518, "answer": "Yes, definitely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 542, "question": "What was your driving motivation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 543, "answer": "Well, I was in a humvee with five other soldiers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 551, "question": "Did you come under a lot of pressure from people in the military, perhaps, and politically as well, not to do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "RB", ",", "CC", "RB", "IN", "RB", ",", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 552, "answer": "No, no, not at any time was I -- I mean, we had criticism and stuff.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 558, "question": "Why would a nice young girl from West Virginia join the Army?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 559, "answer": "I couldn't find -- I wanted a better life for myself.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Army"], "LOCATION": ["West Virginia"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 562, "question": "Did you ever imagine, in your wildest nightmares, that you would one day be on the front line of somewhere like Iraq?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "CD", "NN", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 563, "answer": "No, never, never.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iraq"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 568, "question": "How is that coming along?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 569, "answer": "Good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 581, "question": "I was quite surprised, actually, Is it been getting better for you, slowly but surely?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", ",", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "VBG", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 582, "answer": "It does, because I make it mentally.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 604, "question": "What's the simple idea?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 605, "answer": "Just to get kids reading.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]